Guide to Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records, 1891-2010 COR0003.4.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Corporate and annual events [legacy series], 1974-1982; Series 3
  - College Art Association Reception, 1975 January; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - Preview Parties Biennial, 1975 February; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - First National Bank of Chicago, 1975 September 1; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art in Chicago, 1975 September 19; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - Junior League, 1975 November 4; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - Max Bill Reception, 1975 November 7; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 27)
  - Mobil Posters, 1975 November 20; Series 3 (Box 108, Folders 28-29)
  - Ball Coffee, 1976 January 19; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 30)
  - Docent Cocktail Party, 1976 January 23; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 31)
  - New Friends Luncheon, 1976 February 2; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 32)
  - Department of Interior Reception, 1976 April 26; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 33)
  - AAMD Luncheon, 1976 May 28; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 34)
  - American Association of Museums, 1976 June 2; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 35)
  - Rasenberger Lunch, 1976 September 15; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 36)
  - Herreschoff Reception, 1976 October 8; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 37)
  - Kent Bicentennial Portfolio, 1976 October 16; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 38)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1977 January 19; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 39)
  - Christmas Plan, 1978; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 40)
  - Zandra Rhodes Fashion Benefit, 1979 September 12; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 41)
  - California Art Weisman Dinner, 1979 September 14; Series 3 (Box 108, Folders 42-43)
  - David Lloyed Kreeger Birthday, 1979 September 15; Series 3 (Box 108, Folders 44-45)
  - Daumier/Hammer Dinner, 1979 September 19; Series 3 (Box 108, Folders 46-47)
  - Ford's Theatre Benefit, 1979 October 2; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 48)
  - AT & T Cocktail Reception, 1979 October 11; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 49)
  - George Biddle Opening, 1979 October 17; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 50)
  - Christo, 1979 November 9; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 51)
  - Beaux Art Masquerade Ball, 1979 November 30; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 52)
  - NEA Conference, 1979 December 10; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 53)
  - Family Christmas Party, 1979 December 13; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 54)
  - Polaroid "One of a Kind", 1979 December 18; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 55)
  - Senegalese Art, 1980 February 12 - April 6; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 56)
  - John Alexander, 1980 February 29; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 57)
  - Mime Week, 1980 April 5; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 58)
  - American Indian Tea, 1980 April 15; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 59)
  - Dorothy Phillips Tea, 1980 May 8; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 60)
  - Donor's Dinner, 1980 May 12; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 61)
  - Rosalind Solomon: Washington, 1980 May 15; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 62)
  - "The Surprise Party", 1980 May 20; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 63)
  - Puppets, Art and Entertainment, 1980 June 6; Series 3 (Box 108, Folders 64-65)
  - Corporate Package Evening Masterpiece Exhibition, 1980 June 18; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 66)
  - Philip Duston, 1980 July 18; Series 3 (Box 108, Folder 67)
  - Hammer masterpiece Dinner, 1980 October 1; Series 3 (Box 108, Folders 68-73)
  - Hammer masterpiece Dinner, 1980 October 1; Series 3 (Box 109, Folders 1-4)
  - Guy Pene du Bois Dinner, 1980 October 10; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Wearable Art Show Maria da Conceicao, 1980 October 24; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Christie's Appraisal Event, 1980 November 7 - 8; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Beaux Arts Masquerade Ball, 1980 December 12; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Corcoran Family Christmas Party, 1980 December 18; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Treasures of Nigeria, 1980 December 19; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Champagne Reception, 1981 January 17; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Hammer Reception Leonardo/Presidential Inaugural, 1981 January 17; Series 3 (Box 109, Folders 12-13)
  - Billy Al Bengston Dinner, 1981 January 30; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - 37th Biennial, 1981 February 19; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Ford Theatre Gala Hammer, 1981 March 20; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - P.H. Polk, 1981 March 21; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Cartier Bresson, 1981 April 3 - May 17; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Red Cross Exhibition, 1981 May 17; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Powers/Spalding Modern Dance Concert Benefit, 1981 May 30; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Frank Wright, 1981 June 13 - July 19; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - Charles Peale Polk, 1981 July 17; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Bob Timberlake Dinner, 1981 August 1; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Peter Max Reception, 1981 August 4; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - Neil Jenny Opening and Dinner, 1981 September 11; Series 3 (Box 109, Folders 25-26)
  - Great Adventures Auction, 1981 September; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - Of Time and Place Members Opening, 1981 September 22; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 28)
  - Transamerica - Photographers and the National Parks, 1981 September 22; Series 3 (Box 109, Folders 29-30)
  - Narrative Wood/Marc Cohen Member Opening, 1981 October 9; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 31)
  - Kind and Queen of Spain Reception, 1981 October 14; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 32)
  - Christmas Decorations, 1981 October 29; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 33)
  - U.S. Monopoly Championship, 1982 November 6-8; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 34)
  - Ten Women Photographers White House Conference on Aging, 1981 November 28; Series 3 (Box 109, Folder 35)
- Musical events [legacy series], 1959-1984; Series 4
  Organized into 4 subseries: Performances, Artists vitae, Artists representatives, and Rejection correspondence
  Budgets and other financial information are in Administration, Series 7 under "Finance."
  - Performances, 1959-1983; Series 4 Subseries 1
    This subseries contains information on each of the concerts held at the Corcoran and includes correspondence between Corcoran and the performers, Corcoran and the caterers, programs, PR materials, interdepartmental memos and planning sheets, (pre-event and post-event reports) cost sheets.
    - Children's Music Program David Goldberg - Pianist, 1959; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 36)
    - Children's Music Program Rebecca Spaatz, 1960; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 37)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Washington Cantata Group, 1961 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 38)
    - The United States Army Band, 1961 November 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 39)
    - Old Guard Feife and Drum Corps, 1961 November 18; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 40)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Lola Tilden, 1961 November 26; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 41)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Robert Guralnik, 1961 December 3; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 42)
    - Membership Concerts/Janos Starker, 1961 December 14; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 43)
    - Sunday Free Concerts, 1961-1962; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 44)
    - Membership Concerts/Netherlands Chamber Choir, 1962 January 25; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 45)
    - Membership Concerts/Nicanor Zabaleta, 1962 February 8; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 46)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Donn-Alexandre Feder (Cancelled), 1962 February 11; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 47)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Jack Ervin, 1962 February 11; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 48)
    - Membership Concerts/Paganini Quartet, 1962 February 22; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 49)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Michel Podolski and Christiane Van Acker, 1962 March 4; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 50)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Benjamin Onen (Cancelled), 1962 March 18; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 51)
    - Membership Concerts/I. Musici, 1962 March 22; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 52)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Nancy Cirillo Ruggiero and Mitchell Andrews, 1962 April 29; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 53)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/ Max Isenburgh, 1962 May 20; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 54)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/ Monica Ortiz, 1962 October 7; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 55)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Frances Walker, 1962 October 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 56)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/David Baker, 1962 November 4; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 57)
    - Membership Concerts/David Nadien, 1962 November 15; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 58)
    - Sunday Free Concerts, 1962-1963; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 59)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Richard Morris, 1963 January 6; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 60)
    - Membership Concerts/Vienna Octet, 1963 January 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 61)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Edward J. Hayes, 1963 January 27; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 62)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Herbert Melnick (Cancelled), 1963 February 3; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 63)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Elizabeth Clendenning, 1963 February 10; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 64)
    - Membership Concerts/Paganini Quartet, 1963 February 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 65)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Carl Melton (Cancelled), 1963 March 3; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 66)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Donn-Alexandre Feder, 1963 March 10; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 67)
    - Membership Concerts/Arthur Gold and Robert Fizdale, 1963 March 28; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 68)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/William Montgomery, 1963 April 7; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 69)
    - Membership Concerts/Annie Fischer, 1963 April 11; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 70)
    - Sunday Free Concerts/Ophra Yerushalmi, 1963 April 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 71)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Virginia-Gene Rittenhouse, 1963 October 6; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 72)
    - Amadeus Quartet, 1963 October 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 73)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Martha Braden Jones, 1963 October 20; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 74)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Maria Ines Becerra, 1963 November 3; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 75)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Joan C. Conway, 1963 November 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 76)
    - Membership Concert Series, 1963-1964; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 77)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Marian Burke (Cancelled), 1964 January 5; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 78)
    - Julius Katchen, 1964 January 23; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 79)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Yvonne Easter, 1964 January 26; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 80)
    - Rey de la Torre, 1964 February 6; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 81)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Virginia Rubottom, 1964 February 9; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 82)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Ruth Soskind, 1964 March 1; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 83)
    - Edith Peinemann David Garvey, 1964 March 12; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 84)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Robert Guralnik (Cancelled), 1964 April 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 85)
    - Virtuosi Di Roma, 1964 April 27; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 86)
    - Borodin Quartet, 1964 October 8; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 87)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Cheryl Stern, 1964 October 18; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 88)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Joan Singer Spicknall Janet Rogers, 1964 October 25; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 89)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/ The Little Chorus, 1964 November 1; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 90)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Beth Lee Diaz, 1964 November 15; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 91)
    - Leonard Rose Cellist, 1964 November 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 92)
    - Leonard Rose, 1964 November 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 93)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Clifton Mathews, 1964 December 6; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 94)
    - Membership Concert Series, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 95)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 109, Folder 96)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Beth Jennings, 1965 January 10; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Marian Burke, 1965 January 24; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Marie Francoise Bucquet, 1965 January 31; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Paris Chamber Orchestra, 1965 February 4; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Mary Beck, 1965 February 7; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Bonnie Bogle (Cancelled), 1965 February 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Edith Clifton (Cancelled), 1965 March 7; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - The New York Brass Quintet, 1965 March 18; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Hanoch Greenfeld (Cancelled), 1965 March 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Antient Concerts Sextet, 1965 April 22; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Shenandoah Conservatory Concert Choir, 1965 May 9; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Edmond Rosenfeld, 1965 October 3; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Francoise Vetter, 1965 October 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - The Netherlands Chamber Orchestra, 1965 October 20; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Millicent Tomkins and Russell Woollen, 1965 November 7; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - "Liebeslieder Waltzes" Abbey Singers and Eden and Tamir, 1965 November 18; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Jonathan Parks, Joanna Tousey Parkes, Russell Woollen, 1965 December 12; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Claremont Quartet Receiving the Amati Instruments, 1965 December 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Membership Concerts, 1965-1966; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Ann Amenta-Reiter and David Long, 1966 January 16; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Edward Jackson (Cancelled), 1966 January 16; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Ursula Zollenkopf, 1966 February 6; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Tamas Vasary, 1966 February 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Gerald Rizzer (Cancelled), 1966 February 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Robert Conant, 1966 March; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Catholic University A Cappella Choir, 1966 March 6; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Duo Di Roma, 1966 March 24; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Rosita Casanova and Violeta de la Mata, 1966 April 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - The Renaissance Quartet, 1966 May 12; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Rolf Ermeler (Cancelled), 1966 September 25; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Margaret Rosezarian Harris, 1966 October 16; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folders 31-32)
    - The Clarion Wind Quintet, 1966 October 20; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 33)
    - Tamas Vasary, 1966 October 20; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 34)
    - The Clarion Wind Quintet, 1966 October 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 35)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Janice Nairn, 1966 November 27; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 36)
    - Claremont Quartet, 1966 December 8; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 37)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Linda Chen, 1966 December 11; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 38)
    - Membership Concerts, 1966-1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folders 39-40)
    - Munich Chamber Orchestra, 1967; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 41)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Russell Landgrabe and Phyllis East, 1967 January 22; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 42)
    - The Marlboro Trio, 1967 January 26; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 43)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Hugh Laughlin, 1967 February 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 44)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Hans Prirgnitz, 1967 February 26; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 45)
    - The Galliard Players, 1967 March 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 46)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Washington Woodwind Quintet, 1967 March 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 47)
    - Iowa String Quartet - Receiving the Paganini Strads On Loan from the Corcoran, 1967 April 14; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 48)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Josephine Feagley and Laurence Boyll, 1967 April 16; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 49)
    - Claremont Quartet, 1967 April 20; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 50)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Pina Antonelli, 1967 October 22; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 51)
    - David Amram, 1967 October 23; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 52)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Valentina Kojelis, 1967 November 12; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 53)
    - The Claremont Quartet, 1967 November 16; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 54)
    - Claremont Quartet, 1967 November 16, 1967 December 14, 1968 March 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 55)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Daniel Stolper and David Renner, 1967 November 26; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 56)
    - Iowa String Quartet, 1967 November 30; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 57)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Univ. Of Richmond Choir, 1967 December 10; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 58)
    - Thursday Evening Concerts, 1967-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 59)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts Notification of Acceptance Letters, 1967-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 60)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts, 1967-1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 61)
    - Iowa String Quartet, 1967 November 16, 1968 March 14, 1968 May 2; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 62)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Malinee Peris (Cancelled), 1968 January 14; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 63)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Michael Sellers, 1968 January 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 64)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Potomac String Trio, 1968 February 11; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 65)
    - John Jacob Niles, 1968 February 15; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 66)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Iona Levin, 1968 march 10; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 67)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Fred Coulter, 1968 April 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 68)
    - Barrow Quarter, 1968 October 17; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 69)
    - Washington School of The Ballet, 1968 October 31; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 70)
    - The Elizabethan Consort of Viols, 1968 November 14; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 71)
    - National Association for American composers and Conductors Concert, 1968 November 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 72)
    - An Evening of Contemporary Music, 1968 November 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 73)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts, 1968-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 74)
    - Sunday Afternoon Concerts/Applications to Perform (Series Cancelled June 1968), 1968-1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folders 75-76)
    - Pablo Casals, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 77)
    - Poetry and Jazz Concert Jeremy Robson, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 78)
    - Iowa String Quartet, 1969 January 9, March 20; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 79)
    - Igor Kipins Harpsichord, 1969, January 30; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 80)
    - Adelaide Woodwind Quartet, 1969 February 13; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 81)
    - Washington Brass Choir, 1969 February 27; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 82)
    - Doc Watson, 1969 March 13; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 83)
    - Claremont Quartet, 1969 March 20; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 84)
    - Harold Clayton, 1969 March 22 -23; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 85)
    - The Phoenix Woodwind Quintet, 1969 April 3; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 86)
    - Hermina Petrescu-Stowell, 1969 April 6; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 87)
    - The Claremont Quartet, 1969 May 8; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 88)
    - Love, Cry, Want Mixed-Media, 1969 August 23; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 89)
    - Robert Pritchard Gottschalk Centenary Concert, 1969 October 23; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 90)
    - The Dupont Circle Consortium, 1969 December 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 91)
    - Gaston Neal African Music/Jazz Series, 1969-1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 92)
    - Archie Stewart - Atrium Concerts, 1970-1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 93)
    - Stradivari Quartet, 1970-1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 94)
    - Samuel Rhodes, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 95)
    - Iowa String Quartet Concerts, 1971 May 4; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 96)
    - Bill Harris, 1972 February 12; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 97)
    - Washington Estonian Society Concert, 1972 February 13; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 98)
    - Anechoic Chamber Group, 1972 February 27, March 26; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 99)
    - U.S. Navy String Quartet, 1972 March 12; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 100)
    - Melissa Graybeal Paula Gorelkin, 1972 April 2; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 101)
    - Michael Sellers Dane Rudhyar, 1972 April 23; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 102)
    - Kum Mo Kim, 1972 May 28; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 103)
    - Tokyo String Quartet, 1974-1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 104)
    - Mark Kennerly Clinton, 1975 February 14; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 105)
    - Richard Rieter, 1975 June 14; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 106)
    - The New Hungarian Quartet, 1975 September 27; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 107)
    - Madison Madrigal Singers, 1975 December 21; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 108)
    - National Symphony String Quartet, 1975-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folders 109-110)
    - Tokyo String Quartet, 1975-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folders 111-112)
    - Tony Taylor, 1975-1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 113)
    - The Youth Concerts Foundation, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 114)
    - Michael Hume, 1976 March 13; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 115)
    - Northwood Madrigal Singers, 1976 May 2; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 116)
    - Mark Cohen, 1976 June 5; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 117)
    - Italian Concert, 1976 June 10; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 118)
    - Ingrid and Robert macDonald, 1976 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 119)
    - Arlene Portney Robert Portney, 1976 November 19; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 110, Folder 120)